we're here to talk about the transformation that you have made and
so many people struggle with trying to get healthy and fit and
they become imprisoned in their bodies. And they wake up every day
feeling like they don't wanna be in that body. Or. How did
it start free again. So. You know as an nurse practitioner I'm
trained actually with a license as an acute care nurse practitioner and
a family nurse practitioner and you know being a health care provider
we always think of that we know everything possible about house. And.
It just started to be where I was exhausted over the course
of the past few years I was. To a point where I
was overweight and I just really needed something to change it was
to the point that I had really lost the person I've become
I've always been a really positive person very strong confident and I
just didn't have that anymore. And so it really came to the
point that you know I needed to find. Please that I wanted
to stop settling and I wanted to start living my dreams all
the things that I wanted to do I wasn't capable of doing
that where. Because of my weight and being so tired all the
time. And so I really thought to myself you know what it
this is it I have to find a better version of myself
and you know I wanted to be the author of a different
story so what I did was you know I embrace the pain
and I use that to really burn my fuel to be able
to drive a different course and so I started on a nutritional
cleansing program. And you know I released a total of 70 pounds
I now live in a different body where I have tons of
energy and mental clarity and I wake up like that every day
and you know now I how'd that better version of me you
know I am running 5 miles a day I'm lifting heavier in
the gym than I ever have been in achieving all the things
that I thought that were at the complete impossible. Right. So John
what was the secret for the new you so really what I
started was it it's the whole system and. It it's it's a
nutritional cleansing program and and what it really is it's it's a
roadmap that really can drive you to regain your overall health. And
that's what I love about it a you know it incorporates you
know in natural products I'm a but also a clean eating lifestyle
and you know so we when we think about all of these
fad diets out there you know everybody starts to engage on you
these type of fad diets and they lose a lot of we
and they become scale dependence and so what happens is they lose
all this weight but they don't realize that they're not only losing.
Facts but they're also breaking down their muscle and that puts their
body and a catabolic state and see what happens with that kind
of bollocks state is you know you're breaking down that fat and
muscle and that really shut down our metabolism so for people out
there what really happens is is that they start on these programs
and they lose everything but let me go back to normal eating
they regain all the weight and so than any year third 10
to 20 pounds heavier and then we'll go on a program again
and then we'll gain another 1020 pounds when they start to you
know eat differently again so this is really truly a lifestyle it's
not any type of back fat component at all. Well Jan you
look fantastic thank you. So who can benefit from this nutritional program.
So for this program there is a solution that for every minute
you know all of us out there have 3 different types of
challenges we I can benefit from weight loss we can benefit from
energy in performance and we can also benefit from healthy aging. So
you know what we find is that you know a lot of
athletes can benefit from the energy and performance perspective you know where
they can you deny on their running time and they can increase
their activity in their weights that they're doing in the jam and
then there's also you know different types of products that can help
you from a healthy aging perspective you know as well and then
you've got the weight loss component that I have you really demonstrated
with my own transformation so everyone can benefit from the program absolutely.
So what is the next main component of this program. The main
components of the program is a sh is a chic I minister
Sheikh program combined with a clean eating perspective and I'll go into
the cleaning perspective later on but no in regards to what that
the Sheik is a very different than you know a number of
the other shakes better out there it's really the bass protein that's
available and so what it is it's a it's 100 percent I'm
denatured grasp anyway protein so everybody asks what does that mean right
you know let's break it down into layman's terms so people can
understand it. So the grass fed components means and that the protein
sources not been injected with any any type of toxins at all
and so. That you don't have any antibiotics or steroids or hormones
or anything that have gone into them whatsoever enough protein source and
then to undo natured piece is you know what the process so
that were really extracting from the protein source. So without process you
can always lose a lot of the protein structures that then help
you build the muscle and so what happens is is that you
know that type of protein can help you build you know that
lean muscle when it comes to toxicities you know we want to
be utilizing something that doesn't have a lot of toxins in it
so that's why we focus on the clean eating aspect and we
talk about the grass bad aspect of it you know the reason